what if knowing your health status was
as easy as taking a selfie
thanks to icici lombard it's
unbelievable but true
download icici lombard's il takecare app
your health status is now just a face
scan away
the first of its kind digital feature is
powered by artificial intelligence it
extracts vital signs within seconds
look into the screen scan your face and
get to know your health vitals like
heart rate oxygen saturation respiration
rate blood pressure and more in just two
minutes
everything you need to know on one app
on one device and instantly
scan your face know your health
unbelievable but droop
download the ielts take care app today